택시 창밖으로 번지는 불빛
Lights blurring outside the taxi window
라디오에서 흘러나온 옛날 노래
An old song played on the radio
이 시간엔 모든 게 느려져
At this hour, everything slows down
너한테 갈까 말까 고민만 해
I just agonize over whether to go to you or not
편의점 앞 벤치에 앉아서
Sitting on a bench in front of the convenience store
따뜻한 캔 하나 손에 쥐고
Holding a warm can in my hand
네 연락을 기다리는 건 아닌데
I'm not waiting for your call, but
자꾸 화면을 확인하게 돼
I keep checking my screen
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
Two AM, a night where the frequencies align
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I hear your voice through the static
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we are awake
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
In different places under the same sky
옥상에서 내려다본 골목길
The alley viewed from the rooftop
가로등 하나가 깜빡이고 있어
A streetlamp is flickering
하고 싶은 말은 루프처럼 돌아
The words I want to say loop endlessly
입 밖으론 한마디도 못 꺼내
I can't utter a single word
이어폰 한쪽만 끼고 걸어
I walk with only one earbud in
네가 좋아하던 그 노래 틀어
Playing that song you liked
발걸음이 리듬을 타는 밤
A night where my footsteps follow the rhythm
혼자인데 혼자가 아닌 것 같아
I'm alone, but it doesn't feel like I am
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
Two AM, a night where the frequencies align
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I hear your voice through the static
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we are awake
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
In different places under the same sky
전화할까 말까 세 번째 고민
Should I call or not, my third dilemma
나도 지금 네 번호 보고 있어
I'm also looking at your number right now
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
Two AM, a night where the frequencies align
잡음 속에서 결국 너를 찾아
In the static, I finally find you
이 도시가 잠들어도 우리는 깨어서
Even if this city sleeps, we are awake
같은 주파수로 이어져 있어
Connected by the same frequency